不好意思 各位 这里
Excuse me folks, this is a...
不开放 我们知道
Closed set. We know.
但是我们是猴子的朋友
But we're friends with the monkey, hmm?
早安
Good morning.
嘿 老兄 看我带谁来了
Hey pal, look who I brought!
你的老朋友 亨利伊凡提
Your old friend, Harry Elafonte!
噢 老兄 真惨
Whoa, dude. Burn!
我搞不懂
I don't get it.
他昨天看到我时好像还很开心
He seemed so happy to see me yesterday.
别放在心上 他压力很大
Don't take it personal. He's under a lot of pressure.
你也知道 拍电影的
Y'know, starring in a movie and all.
马塞尔现在算多大牌
Now just how big of a star is Marcel?
用人来比吗 我想他应该是
In human terms? I'd say...
西碧儿雪柏      哇
Cybill Shepherd.        Whoa.
你们是有份演出 还是有妄想症
So you guys in the movie or you just really paranoid?
嘿 塞尔
Hey, Sal?
杰瑞想知道 猴子有没有准备好 拍地铁那场戏
Jerry wants to know if the monkey's ready for the subway set.
不好意思
Excuse me?
杰瑞是导演吗 他是哪一位
Jerry is the director? Which one's he?
坐在导演椅上的那个      知道了
The one in the director's chair?        Gotcha.
菲比 陪我一起走
Pheebs, walk with me.
好
Okay.
为什么要我跟你一起走
How come I'm walking with you?
我们过来这里  是因为可以逃离
Well we're just going over here so that we can get away from
可怕的嗜肉病毒
the horrible flesh eating virus!
看在老天的份上 听我说
For the love of God, woman, listen to me!
他在看吗 他在看吗
Is he looking? Is he looking?
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第13集
超级杯之后（下） The One After the Superbowl
字幕编辑：海盗美剧 小龟快快跑
调校制作：海盗美剧 寒 枫
我们有麻烦了      说吧
We've got a problem.         Tell me.
我没办法帮克莉丝化妆
I can't do Chris's make up.
她不承认自己有胡子
She refuses to acknowledge that she has a moustasche.
很严重吗
Is it bad?
像是眉毛长在嘴上
It looks like one of her eyebrow fell down.
除非谁能说服她把胡子漂白
Now unless someone convinces her to let me bleach it,
不然尚格云顿就得跟盖伯卡普兰亲热了
Jean-Claude Van Damme is gonna be making out with Gabe Kaplan.
我去跟她说
I'll talk to her.
我讨厌演员
I hate actors.
你的迷彩装真不错
Nice camouflage, man.
我差点就没看到你
For a minute there, I almost didn't see you.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你是叫钱德吗      是的
Is your name Chandler?        Yes, yes it is.
你是钱德宾
Chandler Bing.
你是认识我 还是真的就这么厉害
Do you know me or are you just really good at this game?
我是苏西摩斯
I'm Susie Moss.
四年级 戴眼镜的
Fourth grade? Glasses?
我以前随身带一盒动物饼干 像拿着一个皮包一样
I used to carry around a box of animal crackers like a purse?
苏西摩斯
Susie Moss!
是你啊 哇
Right! Yeah! Wow!
你看起来
You look...
真是女大十八变
Great job growing up.
还好你没戴着那个缀满小镜子的牛仔帽
It's nice to see you're not still wearing that denim cap with all the little mirrors on it.
四年级结束以后 我才意识到自己不是拉皮条的
Oh, right, well yeah, I graduated fourth grade and realized I wasn't a pimp.
还记得班级话剧表演吗
Remember the class play?
你掀了我的裙子 让全礼堂的人都看到我的内裤
You pulled up my skirt and the entire auditorium saw my underpants?
对 那时候我用幽默来保护自己
Yes. Back then, I used humor as a defense mechanism.
谢天谢地 我现在不会了
Thank God! I don't do that anymore.
我的天啊      怎么啦 怎么啦
Oh my God!         What? What?
是尚格云顿耶
It's Jean Claude Van Damme.
我不知道他也在这部电影里面 他很帅
I didn't know he was in this movie. He is so hot!
有吗
You think?
布鲁塞尔的肌肉男 尚格云顿
The Muscles from Brussels? Wham Bam Van Damme?
你看过"时空特警"吗
Did you see "Time cop"?
没有 他演得好吗
No. Was he any good in it?
瑞秋 他完全转换了时空耶
Rachel, he like totally changed time!
哇喔
Wow!
你去跟他搭讪啊      少来
So why don't you go talk to him?         Oh. Yeah.
你过去告诉他 他很帅
What, so you go over there, you tell him you think he's cute.
能糟到哪儿去
What's the worst that could happen?
他会听到的
He could hear me.
噢 拜托
Oh, please!
我去帮你说
Okay, I'm doing it for you.
瑞秋 不要 你敢 不行 不行
Oh Rachel don't, don't you dare, don't, don't.
跟他说我会煮菜
Tell him I cook!
不好意思
Excuse me.
嗨      嗨
Hi.         Hi.
听起来可能有点怪
This is gonna sound kind of goofy.
但是 那边我的朋友
But, urn, my friend over there
她很会煮菜
who cooks, by the way.
她觉得你很帅
She thinks you're cute.
你不觉得我帅吗
You don't think I'm cute?
我不知道
I don't know.
你觉得你帅吗
Do you think you're cute?
话题有点扯远了
Okay, we're kinda getting off the track here.
我是来告诉你
I was supposed to come here and tell you
我朋友觉得你很帅
my friend thinks you're cute.
我要怎么回她呢
So, what should I tell her?
你可以跟她说 我觉得她朋友很美
You can tell her I think her friend is cute.
化妆师      他们在叫我 我得走了
Make up!         Oh, that's me. I gotta go.
哦
Oh!
好吧
Okay.
我还得摸你的手臂几次 你才会约我出去呢
So listen, how many times am I gonna have to touch you on the arm before you ask me on a date?
再来一次看看
Well, let's try one more.
这就对了 8点在厄尼餐厅好吗
There you go. Say Ernie's, eight o'clock?
到时候见了
I'll be there.
如果一切顺利的话 说不定这次
And who knows, if things go well, maybe this time.
我会看到你的内裤
I'll get to see your underwear.
竟然没人听到我们的谈话
No one was around to hear that?
他说什么了
So, what'd he say?
真是个混蛋
What a jerk!
我一直在谈你
I kept talking about you.
可是他一直想约我出去
And he kept asking me out.
自然 我拒绝他了
I mean, naturally, you know, I said no.
那么
Well,
还是多谢
thanks, anyway.
他只是一直约我
He just kept asking
一直问 一直问
and asking, asking, asking...
瑞秋 如果你想跟他约会 那就去啊
Rachel, if you, if you wanna go out with him, you can.
虽然我觉得他是个混蛋 但是如果你想去的话
Sound like a big jerk to me if that's what you want to do...
尚格 她答应了 今晚见
Jean Claude, she said yes! I'll see you tonight!
谢谢你
Thank you.
然后尚格带我去酒吧
And then Jean-Claude took me to that place Crossroads.
在那里跟德鲁巴里摩尔聊了一会儿
And that's where we hung out with Drew Barrymore.
哇 她很惹火哦
Oh, man. She's so smoking!
她有很炫的
She's got the greatest set of...
周围没男的喔
No guys around, huh?
有人想喝点什么吗
Anybody need anything?
我要杯浓缩咖啡
Oh, I'll have an espresso.
我自己来好了
Oh, actually I'll get it.
如果要你拿 说不定会被你喝掉
If I ask you to, you'll probably end up drinking it yourself.
她这样说太不公平了      对啊
That is so unfair.         I know.
你怎么可能在抢了云顿之后 还把她的咖啡喝掉
Oh, like you would drink her coffee after what you did to her with Van Damme?
乔伊 今晚我不能跟你打壁球了
Hey Joey, I have to cancel racketball for tonight.
刚刚是马塞尔的训练师
That was Marcel's trainer.
他可以让马塞尔跟我待几个小时
He's gonna let me have him for a couple of hours.
你为了一只猴子放我鸽子
You're blowing me off for a monkey?
我们可以改到星期六再打啊
Hey, we can reschedule for Saturday.
对 除非你又勾搭上一群鸽子
Yeah, unless you hook up with a bunch of pigeons.
嘿
Hey.
拿根叉子刺我吧
Stick a fork in me
我熟了
I am done!
拿叉子刺什么
Stick a fork what?
就像你做牛排的时候
Like when you're cooking a steak.
我不吃肉
Oh, okay, I don't eat meat.
那你怎么知道蔬菜熟了没
Well then, how do you know when vegetables are done?
你吃了就会知道啊
Well you know, you just, you eat them and you can tell.
那就吃我吧 我熟了
Okay, then eat me, I'm done!
我碰到了完美的女人      什么
I've met the perfect woman.         What?
我们在沙发上 卿卿我我
Okay, we're sitting on her couch, we're fooling around.
突然 她对我说
And then suddenly she turns to me and says,
"你想在电梯里做吗"
"Did you ever want to do it in an elevator?"
你说了什么
What did you say?
我相信 我的原话是 哼呀咿
I believe my exact words were "Flaign,en - sten"
我不知道要说什么
I mean I didn't know what to say.
你怎么知道你想不想
How do you know if you wanna do it on an elevator?
你就是知道
Oh, you just know.
我们得走了 30分钟内要到餐厅
Oh, shoot, we gotta go, got a reservation in thirty minutes.
不 不 不 不 不
Oh no no no no no no no no no no.
我计划做的事 最多不会超过两三分钟
You see, what I had planned shouldn't take more than two, three minutes tops.
两百秒的激情 我们得走了
Two hundred seconds of passion! We gotta go.
不过
But...
我有个主意
Here's an idea.
你穿过女人的内裤吗
Have you ever worn women's underwear?
其实穿过
Well, yes, actually.
可是我穿的是爱德娜阿姨的
But they were my Aunt Edna's.
而且一共有三个人一起穿
And there were three of us in there.
如果你今晚吃饭时
Well I was thinking it would be kinda sexy,
穿我的内裤 一定会很性感
if you wore mine tonight at dinner.
你要我穿你的内裤
You want me to wear your panties?
可以吗
Could you?
如果我穿你的内裤
Well, if I was wearing your underwear,
那你要穿什么
then what would you be wearing?
你太棒了
You're swell!
你看 我做了马塞尔最爱的香蕉蛋糕
Check it out. I made Marcel's favorite dish, banana cake...
噢      还加了虫虫
Ooh.         with mealworm.
蜡烛
Candle.
你想今晚会发生什么事呢
What do you think is gonna happen here tonight?
喂
Hello.
你好 你准备要过来了吗
Oh, hi, are you on your way over...
哦
Oh!
没关系 我理解 猴子工作很忙
No, no. I understand. A monkey's gotta work.
没关系
It's no big deal.
我也没特别准备什么
lt's not like I had anything special planned, you know.
好 好 再见
Yeah, okay. Okay. Okay, bye.
瑞秋 你先说吧
Okay. Rachel, why don't you start talking first?
好吧 我觉得 她这样是完全没道理的
All right. I feel that this is totally unjustified.
她说我可以的 我又没做什么
She gave me the green light, I did nothing...
你以为 我在电视荧幕上看不到你吗
Do you think I can't see you in the TV set?
摩妮卡 你有什么想说的
Alright Monica, if there is something that you would like to share...
你没权利跟他出去
You know, you had no right to go out with him!
这太荒谬了      你出卖我
That's the most ridiculous.         You sold me out!
我没有      你就是有
I did not sell you out!         You absolutely.
你能让我说完吗
Would you let me talk!
你刚刚弹我的头
Did you just flick me?
因为你不让我说完
OK, well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was jus...
很痛耶
Ow, that hurt!
不要弹了
Quit flicking!
你才不要弹了      你先弹我的
Ow! Stop flicking!        You flicked me first!
不要这样
Okay, no, no.
Let's not do this!
想点快乐的事情 别打了
Come on. Happy thoughts. No! No!
快乐的事情 快乐的事情
Happy thoughts! Happy thoughts!
够了 老娘要出手了
OK, now I'm gonna kick some ass!
好 你们都别闹了 我就放手
All right. Now, I will let go if you both stop.
你要怎样 要我不再见他吗 你就这样想的 对不对
Oh, what do you, you want me to stop seeing him, is that what you want?
嗯哈
Uhhuh.
你要我打电话给他
You want me to just call him up,
跟他说他应该跟你约会
and tell him that you're seeing him instead?
你是要这样吗      对
Is that what you want?        Okay.
你就是要这样      没错
Oh, that's what you want!        Yes!
好      好
Fine!         Fine!
很好
There we go.
如果我们在监狱 你们可以当我的小喽
You know what? If we were in prison, you guys would be like my bitches.
谢谢你们让我加入
Thanks for letting me tag along tonight, you guys.
别客气啦
Forget about it.
你怎么样      勉强撑着
How you doing there, squirmy?         I'm hanging in.
有点跑出来了
And a little out.
你是导演的助理啊
So assistant to the director?
这个工作真棒 你的责任一定很大
That's a really exciting job. I mean, you must have a ton of cool responsibilities.
我不负责选角
I have nothing to do with casting.
你们想吃什么
So, what are you guys gonna eat?
为什么我满脑子只想着把冰块含在嘴里
How come all I can think about is putting that ice in my mouth.
然后舔遍你全身呢
and licking you all over?
因为我上的是男子中学 现在上帝要补偿我了
Because I went to an all boys high school, and God is making up for it?
我现在就想要你
I want you right here
在这里
right now.
此时此刻
Right now, right here?
你不觉得 这里算是公共场合吗
Don't you think we're in kind of a public place?
这里真有虾呢
They do have the shrimp.
到洗手间等我
Meet me in the bathroom.
我现在要去洗手间
I'm going to the bathroom now.
来吧
Come on.
好了 先生
All right, mister.
让我看看你的内裤吧
Let's see those panties.
好啊
Alrighty.
你知道怎样会更性感吗
But you know what would be even sexier?
怎样
What?
如果你没把上衣塞进去的话
If you didn't have your shirt tucked into them.
好 现在呢 我要看你只穿内裤的样子
All right. Now, I would like to see you wearing nothing but them.
把衣服脱掉
Take your clothes off.
我要提醒你
But, uh, I hope you realize this means
这样会错过服务生介绍特餐的时间
we're gonna miss hearing about the specials.
来 快点
Come on, hurry!
你是要我做得最快 还是要我做得最好
Hey, do you want this done quick or done right?
好了 转过身去 我要看你的背后
All right, turn around. I wanna see you from behind.
有人一直跟着健身录影带做运动喔
Oh oh. Somebody's been doing his Buns of Steel video.
你要我夹紧什么东西吗
So you want me to, uh, clench anything or...
苏西
Susie?
这是你四年级的报应
This is for the fourth grade.
你什么意思呀     我什么意思
Huh? What do you mean?         What do I mean?
什么"什么意思"
What do you mean what do I mean?
我的意思是内裤 先生 我就是这个意思
I mean underpants, mister! That's what I mean!
什么 什么意思
What? What do you mean?
我的裙子
My skirt!
你掀了 小孩都笑了
You lifted. Kids laughing!
我一直到十八岁都是内裤苏西
I was Susie Underpants till I was eighteen!
那是四年级的事情
That was in fourth grade!
你怎么会气到现在
How could you still be upset about that?
那么
Well...
你二十年后打电话给我
Why don't you call me in 20 years and
告诉我 你还气不气今天的事吧
and tell me if you're still upset about this.
你要知道 你的内裤我不会还你了喔
Alright, I hope you realize you're not getting these underpants back!
我真是不敢相信
I can't believe this.
两个星期前 我还在看"绝命杀阵"
Just two weeks ago, I was watching "Sudden Death".
现在我却在跟尚格云顿约会
And now I'm on a date with Jean Claude Van Damme.
你能打扁那个家伙吗
Can you beat up that guy?
当然
Yeah.
你可以打倒那个人吗      当然
Can you beat up that guy?         Sure.
实在是太棒了
Oh, this is so wild.
我得承认 我有点吃惊你会答应跟我出来
Y'know, I gotta admit, I was kinda surprised that you agreed to go on a blind date.
通常我是不会答应的
Normally, I would not do it.
是吗
Yeah?
那为什么会为我破例
What made you make the exception for me?
因为瑞秋跟我说
Because Rachel told me,
你非常想跟我和德鲁巴里摩尔来个三人行
you were dying to have a threesome with me and, uh, Drew Barrymore.
对了 德鲁有些原则
By the way, Drew has some ground rules and...
快跟我说对不起      不要
Say you're sorry!         No!
说
Say it!
不 我不要
No! I'm not gonna!
说 说啊 很好
Say it! Say it! Great!
瑞秋
Rachel,
跟我说对不起 不然你的毛衣就要毁了
say you're sorry or your sweater gets it.
那是我最爱的毛衣 是我第三次约会必穿的毛衣
That is my favorite sweater! That is my third date sweater!
说对不起
Say you're sorry.
你要玩是吧 那就来玩吧
Okay, you wanna play? Okay,let's play.
那就玩吧
Let's play.
你想干嘛
What are you gonna do?
把毛衣还给我 不然我就酱腌皮包
Give me back my sweater or it's handbag marinara.
你没那个胆
You don't have the guts.
是吗 至少我不会没胆 跟喜欢的人说他很帅
Yeah? At least I wasnt too chicken to tell some guy I thought he was cute.
住手 别再疯了
Oh. all right, stop! Stop the madness!
这太荒唐了
This is crazy!
你们谁还能记起来 一开始为了什么在吵
Who can even remember why this even started in the first place?
对 没错
Yes, that's right.
但是
But still,
看看你的包包
Look at your purse!
看看你的毛衣
Look at your sweater!
看看你们自己
Look at yourselves!
我会帮你把毛衣补好
I'll help you fix your sweater.
我会帮你
I'll help you
把包包丢掉
throw out your purse.
很抱歉 我强迫你不要跟他约会
I'm sorry that I made you stop seeing him.
很抱歉 我明知道你喜欢他 却还是跟他出去
I'm sorry I went out with him when I knew you liked him.
我很抱歉 我借了你的手套
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gloves.
乔伊
Joey?
妈
Ma?
乔伊
Joey!
钱德
Chandler?
你怎么还在这儿 我以为你们已经走了
What are you still doing here? I thought you guys took off.
不 不 不 是她走了 也拿走了我的衣服
She took off with my clothes!
你光着身子吗      也不完全是
Are you naked in there?         Well, not exactly.
我穿着丁字裤
I'm wearing panties.
你一直穿丁字裤的吗
You, uh, always wear panties?
不 这是第一次
No. no. This is the first time.
哇 你运气也太差了吧
Wow. Talk about your bad luck!
才第一次试穿丁字裤 衣服就被人偷走了
I mean, the first time you try panties and someone walks off with your clothes.
不是我试着穿的
I was not trying them out.
是苏西要我穿的
Susie asked me to wear them.
让我看看
Let me see!
不要 我才不要给任何人看
No! I'm not letting you or anybody else see ever!
好啦 好啦
All right, all right!
哇
Wow!
有人在用"牙线"喔
Someone's flossing!
乔伊 不是每个人都喜欢你这样做
Joey, some people don't like that.
钱德穿着丁字裤耶
Chandler's wearing panties.
什么
What?
我看看      不要 你不用看吧
Let me see!         No no. You don't have to see!
嗨 翘臀
Hi, tushy!
谁把内裤借我穿
Alright, one of you give me your underpants.
不行
Oh. no.
我帮不了你 我根本没穿
Can't help you, I'm not wearing any.
你怎么会没穿内裤
How can you not be wearing any underwear?
因为看到一个男的穿了粉红丁字裤 让我火热难耐
Oh.I'm getting heat from the guy in the hot pink thong.
罗斯 我出50块买你的内裤
Alright, look, Ross. I'll give you 50 dollars for your underpants.
嗨
Hi.
菲比 牛奶用完给我好吗
Hey Phoebs, can I have the milk after you?
我快加好了 拉住裤裤不要急嘛
I'm almost done with it. Keep your panties on.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
我被电影剧组录取啦      耶
And I'm in the movie!         Hey.
你怎么办到的
What happened?
有个演病人的生病了
One of the virus victims called in sick.
凯西跟导演推荐我 我要死在轮床上啦
So Cathy recommended me and boom! I'm dying on a gurney!
嘿
Hey!
罗斯 马塞尔拍完最后一场戏了
Oh Ross, Marcel just finished his last scene
你如果想跟他道别 要快点去
if you want to go down there and say goodbye.
没关系 他大概还要参加杀青派对之类的
That's okay. I mean, he's probably got, you know, parties to go to and stuff.
你知道的 他已经有了新的生活
You know, he's moved on.
本来就应该这样的 对吧
That's the way it goes, right?
我的天啊
Oh my God!
怎么了
What?
我想要写首歌 纪念这整件事
You know, I think I want to write a song about all this.
是吗      是啊
Oh, yeah?         Yeah.
可是我的吉他有根弦断了
Ooh except one of the strings on my guitar is broken.
钱德 我能借你的丁字裤吗
Hey, Chandler, can I borrow your Gstring?
你等着说这句话等多久了
How long you been waiting to say that?
大概二十分钟吧
About 20 minutes!
你们还搞不清楚状况吗 这个人快死了
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
停
Cut!
你们还搞不清楚状况吗 这个人快死了
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
停
Cut!
你们还搞不清楚状况吗 这个人快死了
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
妈咪
Mommy!
你们还搞不清楚状况吗 这个人已经死了
Can't you see what's going on? This man is dead!
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧